

Contact
darkowsky@mail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/darkowsky (LinkedIn)

Certifications

The complete digital marketing course - 12 Courses in 1

Video Marketing

TikTok Marketing 2023: Grow Your Account & Master TikTok Ads

Workshop: Google Advertising for Real Professionals

Darko Stojkovski

Digital marketing at Makedonijalek Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

Summary

Digital Marketing warrior with battle-tested experience in building, maintaining, and running successful digital marketing campaigns.

My client-centered campaigns are aimed at achieving mission-critical goals like improving brand awareness and presence.

As a collaborative and creative soldier, I'm highly skilled at managing digital marketing content and using various social media and email marketing tools. I also take on special ops, creating photography and video products tailored to the client's needs.

When not in the digital trenches, I enjoy solving all kinds of digital problems and exercising my creativity in the field of audio and visual art, photography, videography, audio editing, audio reactive visuals, portrait photography and bodyscapes.

Experience

Makedonijalek
Digital Marketing
September 2020 - Present (3 years)

Golemi & Mali Founder August 2016 - Present (7 years 1 month) Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

Association for Democratic Advancement - Democracy Lab Video Producer September 2021 - September 2021 (1 month) Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

Earthly Humans
Co-Founder
2018 - 2018 (less than a year)

Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

Desonanz Festival
Event Photographer/Videographer
2018 - 2018 (less than a year)
Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

Lesnovo Art Colony Photographer 2012 - 2014 (2 years)

The Woodstock - Unique Wooden Furniture Product Photographer/ Catalog Designer 2013 - 2013 (less than a year)

Education

Faculty of Philosophy - Skopje / Филозофски факултет - Скопје Bachelor of Arts - BA, Sociology · (2009 - 2015)

Medical High School
· (2005 - 2009)